A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1958-1970 FA400
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1970
  - United States, 1970/200
    - United States, Agency for International Development (Agriculture) (Reel 27, Frame 1)
    - United States, Agency for International Development (A-C) (Reel 27, Frame 128)
    - United States, Agency for International Development (D-Z) (Reel 27, Frame 269)
    - United States, Agriculture (A-W) (Reel 27, Frame 500)
    - United States, Health Education and Welfare (B-W) (Reel 27, Frame 768)
    - United States (A-N) (Reel 27, Frame 879)
    - United States (P-S) (Reel 27, Frame 1103)
    - United States Center for ASSITEJ (Reel 28, Frame 1)
    - United States Information Agency (E-M) (Reel 28, Frame 25)
    - United States-Japan Cooperative Medical Science Program (Virus Diseases) (Reel 28, Frame 29)
    - United States Junior Chamber of Commerce (Reel 28, Frame 39)
    - United States-South Africa Leader Exchange Program (Reel 28, Frame 50)
    - University (A-B) (Reel 28, Frame 90)
    - University of California (A-I) (Reel 28, Frame 273)
    - University of California (J-M) (Reel 28, Frame 417)
    - University of California (P-Y) (Reel 28, Frame 629)
    - University ( C ) (Reel 28, Frame 754)
    - University of Florida (Tropical Agriculture) (Reel 28, Frame 990)
    - University of Florida (M-Y) (Reel 28, Frame 1119)
    - University (D-G) (Reel 28, Frame 1130)
    - University of Hawaii (C-V) (Reel 29, Frame 1)
    - University of Illinois (A-Y) (Reel 29, Frame 115)
    - University (I-L) (Reel 29, Frame 278)
    - University (Ma) (Reel 29, Frame 351)
    - University of Michigan (A-W) (Reel 29, Frame 411)
    - University of Minnesota (B-W) (Reel 29, Frame 577)
    - University (Mi) (Reel 29, Frame 722)
    - University of Notre Dame (C-W) (Reel 29, Frame 760)
    - University (N) (Reel 29, Frame 883)
    - University (O-P) (Reel 29, Frame 997)
    - University of Southern California (Public Administration) (Reel 30, Frame 1)
    - University of Southern California (G-U) (Reel 30, Frame 157)
    - University of Southern California, Ocean Resources Development (Supplementary Material) (Reel 30, Frame 264)
    - University of Southern California, Urban Affairs (Supplementary Material) (Reel 30, Frame 530)
    - University (R-S) (Reel 30, Frame 636)
    - University (T) (Reel 30, Frame 888)
    - University of Virginia (Kolodziej, Edward) (Reel 30, Frame 902)
    - University (U-V) (Reel 30, Frame 1027)
    - University of Washington (B-W) (Reel 31, Frame 1)
    - University of Wisconsin (A-W) (Reel 31, Frame 155)
    - Urban Communications Institute (Arts Development) (Reel 31, Frame 362)
    - Urban Institute (Gorham, William) (Reel 31, Frame 663)
    - U (Reel 31, Frame 803)
    - Va (Reel 31, Frame 1033)
    - Ve-Vo (Reel 32, Frame 1)
    - Watkins, Gordon R. (Reel 32, Frame 106)
    - W-Wa (Reel 32, Frame 295)
    - Western (C-M) (Reel 32, Frame 464)
    - We (Reel 32, Frame 515)
    - Wh (Reel 32, Frame 701)
    - Wichita, Education (January-May) (Reel 32, Frame 710)
    - Wichita, Education (June) (Reel 32, Frame 963)
    - Wichita, Education (July-August) (Reel 33, Frame 1)
    - Wichita, Education (September) (Reel 33, Frame 320)
    - Wichita, Education (October-December) (Reel 33, Frame 619)
    - Wi (Reel 33, Frame 734)
    - Wo-Wr (Reel 33, Frame 874)
    - Y-Z (Reel 33, Frame 960)
    - United States - Medical Studies, 1970/200.A
      - A-J (Reel 34, Frame 1)
      - M-O (Reel 34, Frame 92)
      - S-Y (Reel 34, Frame 243)
    - United States - Nursing Program, 1970/200.C
      - Boston University (Nursing School) (Reel 34, Frame 399)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/200.D
      - C-U (Reel 34, Frame 416)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/200.E
      - Hamilton, David W. (Reel 34, Frame 448)
    - United States - Declinations, 1970/200.F
      - Serebrier, Jose (Reel 34, Frame 450)
    - United States - Humanitites and Arts, 1970/200.R
      - Playwrights (A-G) (Reel 34, Frame 560)
      - Playwrights (H-L) (Reel 34, Frame 859)
      - Playwrights (M-U) (Reel 34, Frame 968)
      - Playwrights (W-Z) (Reel 35, Frame 1)
      - A-S (Reel 35, Frame 118)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1970/200.S
      - C-U (Reel 35, Frame 170)
    - United States - Virus Studies, 1970/200.V
      - Johns Hopkins University (Reel 35, Frame 210)
    - United States - Schistosomiasis, 1970/200.W
      - J-T (Reel 35, Frame 212)
  - Philippines, 1970/242
    - Administration (Reel 35, Frame 253)
    - A-P (Reel 35, Frame 379)
    - R-U (Reel 35, Frame 563)
    - Philippines - Medical Sciences, 1970/242.A
      - University of the Philippines (Reel 35, Frame 830)
    - Philippines - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/242.E
      - A-V (Reel 35, Frame 833)
  - Puerto Rico, 1970/243
    - A-U (Reel 35, Frame 889)
    - Puerto Rico - Medical Studies, 1970/243.A
      - University of Puerto Rico (Medical School) (Reel 35, Frame 1017)
    - Puerto Rico - Schistosomiasis, 1970/243.W
      - Puerto Rico (Reel 35, Frame 1040)
  - Virgin Islands, 1970/257
    - Professional Development Institute (Reel 35, Frame 1047)
  - Internship Program - Minority School Superintendents, 1970/260
    - Candidates (A-W) (Reel 35, Frame 1049)
  - Playwrights in Residence, 1970/272
    - Lortz, Richard (Reel 35, Frame 1098)
  - South America and Central America, 1970/300
    - Administration (Reel 35, Frame 1103)
    - I-L (Reel 36, Frame 1)
    - South America and Central America - Medical Studies, 1970/300.A
      - Pan American Conference on Medical Education (Reel 36, Frame 152)
    - South America and Central America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/300.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 36, Frame 162)
  - Argentina, 1970/301
    - B-T (Reel 36, Frame 176)
    - Argentina - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/301.E
      - Calderoni, Atilio Victor (Reel 36, Frame 279)
  - Bolivia, 1970/303
    - D-U (Reel 36, Frame 288)
    - Bolivia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/303.D
      - Agriculture (A-G) (Reel 36, Frame 292)
    - Bolivia - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/303.E
      - Acha, Orlando (Reel 36, Frame 316)
  - Brazil, 1970/305
    - Agriculture (Reel 36, Frame 319)
    - A-K (Reel 36, Frame 324)
    - University of Minas Gerais (Veterinary Medicine) (Reel 36, Frame 448)
    - M-U (Reel 36, Frame 493)
    - Brazil - Medical Sciences, 1970/305.A
      - C-U (Reel 36, Frame 608)
    - Brazil - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/305.D
      - Agriculture (Gibler, John W.) (Reel 36, Frame 711)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/305.E
      - B-N (Reel 36, Frame 716)
  - Chile, 1970/309
    - Administration (Reel 36, Frame 744)
    - A-W (Reel 36, Frame 883)
    - Chile - Nursing, 1970/309.C
      - National School of Nursing, Lima (Reel 36, Frame 969)
    - Chile - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/309.E
      - C-T (Reel 36, Frame 973)
  - Colombia, 1970/311
    - Administration (Reel 36, Frame 1012)
    - Universidad del Valle (A-T) (Reel 36, Frame 1016)
    - A-V (Reel 37, Frame 1)
    - Colombia - Medical Sciences, 1970/311.A
      - Cali Medical School (Pediatrics) (Reel 37, Frame 149)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/311.D
      - A-C (Reel 37, Frame 152)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/311.E
      - Colombia (Reel 37, Frame 164)
      - A-G (Reel 37, Frame 193)
      - J-Z (Reel 37, Frame 313)
  - Costa Rica, 1970/313
    - Gutierrez, J. R. (Reel 37, Frame 476)
    - Costa Rica - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/313.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 37, Frame 479)
  - Ecuador, 1970/317
    - University of Guayaquil (Montalvan C., Juan A.) (Reel 37, Frame 481)
    - Ecuador - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/317.E
      - Ecuador (Reel 37, Frame 485)
      - Ibarra, Jorge (Reel 37, Frame 487)
  - Guatemala, 1970/319
    - N-U (Reel 37, Frame 498)
    - Guatemala - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/319.D
      - Agriculture (Fumagalli C., Astolfo) (Reel 37, Frame 508)
  - Honduras, 1970/321
    - Escuela Agricola Panamericana (Reel 37, Frame 531)
    - Honduras - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/321.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 37, Frame 534)
  - Mexico, 1970/323
    - A-I (Reel 37, Frame 536)
    - L-Z (Reel 37, Frame 598)
    - Mexico - Medical Sciences, 1970/323.A
      - Hospital Infantil (Reel 37, Frame 834)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/323.E
      - Mexico (Reel 37, Frame 836)
      - A-Z (Reel 37, Frame 845)
  - Nicaragua, 1970/325
    - Castilla, Osmundo (Reel 37, Frame 884)
  - Panama, 1970/327
    - G-H (Reel 37, Frame 900)
  - Paraguay, 1970/329
    - Peroni, Guillermo F. (Reel 37, Frame 912)
    - Paraguay - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/329.D
      - Agriculture (Barros, Nelson) (Reel 37, Frame 919)
  - Peru, 1970/331
    - A-Y (Reel 37, Frame 939)
    - Peru - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/331.D
      - Agriculture (Baracco, Abelardo) (Reel 38, Frame 1)
    - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/331.E
      - C-Q (Reel 38, Frame 4)
  - El Salvador, 1970/333
    - El Salvador - Medical Sciences, 1970/333.A
      - University of Salvador (Medical School) (Reel 38, Frame 32)
    - El Salvador - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/333.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 38, Frame 36)
  - Uruguay, 1970/337
    - Pereya-Suarez, Esther (Reel 38, Frame 39)
    - Uruguay - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/337.D
      - Agriculture (Ortiz, Pola) (Reel 38, Frame 45)
  - Venezuela, 1970/339
    - G-U (Reel 38, Frame 47)
    - Venezuela - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/339.D
      - Agriculture (Ortiz, Paula) (Reel 38, Frame 60)
  - Great Britain, 1970/400
    - C-O (Reel 38, Frame 62)
  - England, 1970/401
    - A-L (Reel 38, Frame 89)
    - M-R (Reel 38, Frame 274)
    - S-W (Reel 38, Frame 429)
  - Ireland, 1970/403
    - A-T (Reel 38, Frame 676)
  - Scotland, 1970/405
    - University (E-G) (Reel 38, Frame 682)
  - Wales, 1970/407
    - D-U (Reel 38, Frame 719)
  - Australia, 1970/410
    - A-W (Reel 38, Frame 731)
    - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1970/410.A
      - Australian National University (Medical School) (Reel 38, Frame 858)
  - New Zealand, 1970/418
    - Wodzicki, Kazamiers (Reel 38, Frame 860)
  - Fiji, 1970/419
    - University of the South Pacific (Reel 38, Frame 863)
    - Fiji - Medical Sciences, 1970/419.A
      - Fiji School of Medicine (Reel 38, Frame 874)
  - Caribbean Region, 1970/420
    - A-M (Reel 38, Frame 876)
    - Caribbean Region - Medical Sciences, 1970/420.A
      - Caribbean Committee for Bilharzia Research (Reel 38, Frame 1000)
  - Guyana, 1970/423
    - University of Guyana (Irvine, Dennis H.) (Reel 38, Frame 1072)
    - Guyana - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/423.E
      - Chin, Algernon (Reel 38, Frame 1086)
  - Belize, 1970/425
    - Rautenberg, J. E. (Reel 38, Frame 1089)
  - Canada, 1970/427
    - A-C (Reel 39, Frame 1)
    - E-K (Reel 39, Frame 227)
    - M-N (Reel 39, Frame 311)
    - Q-Y (Reel 39, Frame 439)
    - Canada - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/427.D
      - Agriculture (Anstey, Tom) (Reel 39, Frame 564)
  - Bermuda, 1970/430
    - Bermuda Biological Station for Research (Scott, George T.) (Reel 39, Frame 566)
  - Jamaica, 1970/437
    - University of the West Indies (M-P) (Reel 39, Frame 602)
    - Jamaica - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/437.D
      - Agriculture (Stuart, W. G.) (Reel 39, Frame 637)
  - Trinidad and Tobago, 1970/451
    - C-T (Reel 39, Frame 639)
  - Winward Islands, 1970/455
    - H-S (Reel 39, Frame 665)
  - South Asia Region, 1970/460
    - South Asia Region - Declinations Outside Program, 1970/460.FO
      - Bhutan (Health) (Reel 39, Frame 738)
  - Sri Lanka, 1970/462
    - C-V (Reel 39, Frame 740)
    - Sri Lanka - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/462.D
      - Agriculture (Kanakaratne, Neville) (Reel 39, Frame 755)
    - Sri Lanka - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/462.E
      - Sivanayagam, T. (Reel 39, Frame 761)
  - Hong Kong, 1970/463
    - C-U (Reel 39, Frame 764)
  - India, 1970/464
    - A-H (Reel 39, Frame 783)
    - I (Reel 39, Frame 872)
    - J-U (Reel 39, Frame 965)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1970/464.A
      - All-India Institute of Medical Sciences (B-R) (Reel 40, Frame 1)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/464.E
      - 464E (Reel 40, Frame 27)
      - P-S (Reel 40, Frame 32)
  - Pakistan, 1970/465
    - E-R (Reel 40, Frame 48)
    - Pakistan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/465.D
      - Corn (Reel 40, Frame 79)
  - Iraq, 1970/470
    - Alaka, Anwar (Reel 40, Frame 85)
  - New Guinea and Papua, 1970/472
    - P-U (Reel 40, Frame 87)
  - Malaysia, 1970/473
    - H-Y (Reel 40, Frame 90)
    - Malaysia - Medical Sciences, 1970/473.A
      - University (M-S) (Reel 40, Frame 100)
  - Nepal, 1970/474
    - Nepal - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/474.D
      - Agriculture (Basnyat, N. B.) (Reel 40, Frame 111)
  - Africa, 1970/475
    - A-C (Reel 40, Frame 129)
    - Africa - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/475.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 40, Frame 199)
  - Kenya, 1970/476
    - East African Agriculture and Forestry Research Organization (Reel 40, Frame 202)
    - A-H (Reel 40, Frame 386)
    - J-U (Reel 40, Frame 533)
    - Kenya - Medical Sciences, 1970/476.A
      - University College, Nairobi (Medical School) (Reel 40, Frame 609)
    - Kenya - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/476.D
      - A-U (Reel 40, Frame 620)
    - Kenya - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/476.E
      - G-O (Reel 40, Frame 651)
  - East Africa Region, 1970/477
    - Administration (Reel 40, Frame 708)
    - E-W (Reel 40, Frame 898)
    - East Africa Region - Declinations, 1970/477.F
      - East African Medical Research Council (Conference) (Reel 40, Frame 968)
  - Mauritius, 1970/478
    - Economic Planning (Reel 40, Frame 970)
  - Malawi, 1970/482
    - H-U (Reel 40, Frame 972)
  - Rhodesia, 1970/483
    - H-R (Reel 40, Frame 992)
  - North Africa Region, 1970/485
    - Shope, Robert E. (Supplementary Material) (Reel 40, Frame 1008)
  - South Africa Region, 1970/487
    - B-U (Reel 40, Frame 1020)
  - Republic of South Africa, 1970/489
    - A-S (Reel 40, Frame 1038)
  - Uganda, 1970/492
    - Makerere College (B-M) (Reel 41, Frame 1)
    - B-S (Reel 41, Frame 218)
    - Uganda - Medical Sciences, 1970/492.A
      - Makerere College (Medical School) (Reel 41, Frame 366)
    - Uganda - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/492.D
      - Agriculture (Nsueuga, H. S. K.) (Reel 41, Frame 429)
    - Uganda - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/492.E
      - B-S (Reel 41, Frame 431)
    - Uganda - Social Sciences, 1970/492.S
      - Makerere University (Political Science) (Reel 41, Frame 500)
  - West Africa Region, 1970/495
    - O-W (Reel 41, Frame 529)
    - West Africa Region - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/495.D
      - Agriculture (Glele, Adrien A.) (Reel 41, Frame 631)
    - West Africa Region - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/495.E
      - Sere, D. (Reel 41, Frame 635)
  - Ghana, 1970/496
    - B-U (Reel 41, Frame 637)
    - Ghana - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/496.E
      - Saffu, Yaw (Reel 41, Frame 667)
  - Nigeria, 1970/497
    - Administration (Reel 41, Frame 671)
    - A-M (Reel 41, Frame 769)
    - N-T (Reel 41, Frame 865)
    - University of Ibadan (A-H) (Reel 41, Frame 959)
    - University of Ibadan (L-S) (Reel 41, Frame 1075)
    - U-W (Reel 42, Frame 1)
    - Nigeria - Medical Sciences, 1970/497.A
      - University of Ibadan (Medical School) (Reel 42, Frame 161)
    - Nigeria - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/497.D
      - A-U (Reel 42, Frame 193)
    - Nigeria - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/497.E
      - Fellowships (Reel 42, Frame 327)
      - A-U (Reel 42, Frame 333)
    - Nigeria - Declinations, 1970/497.F
      - Kolawole, M. I. (Reel 42, Frame 459)
    - Nigeria - Social Sciences, 1970/497.S
      - University of Ibadan (E-S) (Reel 42, Frame 478)
  - Sierra Leone, 1970/499
    - University College of Sierra Leone (Porter, Arthur T.) (Reel 42, Frame 500)
  - France, 1970/500
    - A-N (Reel 42, Frame 506)
    - Organization for Economic Co-operation and Development (M-Y) (Reel 42, Frame 552)
    - P-U (Reel 42, Frame 706)
  - French Guiana, 1970/507
    - Pasteur Institute (Serie, Charles) (Reel 42, Frame 753)
  - Vietnam, 1970/509
    - Vietnam - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/509.D
      - Agriculture (Binh, Nguyen Hai) (Reel 42, Frame 757)
  - Cambodia, 1970/513
    - E-P (Reel 42, Frame 761)
  - Guinea, 1970/525
    - Keita, Sidiki K. (Reel 42, Frame 765)
  - Ivory Coast, 1970/527
    - Ivory Coast - Medical Sciences, 1970/527.A
      - University of Abidjan (Medical School) (Reel 42, Frame 769)
    - Ivory Coast - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/527.D
      - Agriculture (Sawadogo, Abdoulaye) (Reel 42, Frame 771)
  - Mali, 1970/530
    - Mali - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/530.D
      - Mali (Animal Sciences) (Reel 42, Frame 775)
  - Senegal, 1970/531
    - A-P (Reel 42, Frame 851)
    - Senegal - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/531.E
      - Ndiaye, D. (Reel 42, Frame 875)
  - Tunisia, 1970/539
    - Agriculture (Essafi, Abdelhamid) (Reel 42, Frame 877)
  - Asia, 1970/600
    - Administration (Reel 42, Frame 894)
    - Upland Crops Institute (Reel 42, Frame 897)
    - Asia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/600.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 42, Frame 899)
  - Taiwan, 1970/605
    - Asian Vegetable Development Center (Reel 42, Frame 913)
  - Japan, 1970/609
    - A-T (Reel 42, Frame 928)
    - Japan - Nursing, 1970/609.C
      - St. Luke's International Hospital (Reel 42, Frame 1029)
    - Japan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/609.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 42, Frame 1033)
  - Korea, 1970/613
    - E-K (Reel 42, Frame 1037)
  - Thailand, 1970/617
    - Administration (Reel 43, Frame 1)
    - A-K (Reel 43, Frame 221)
    - Nutrition Graduate Training Program (Reel 43, Frame 337)
    - M-T (Reel 43, Frame 453)
    - U-V (Reel 43, Frame 565)
    - Thailand - Medical Sciences, 1970/617.A
      - R-T (Reel 43, Frame 634)
    - Thailand - Nursing, 1970/617.C
      - Ramathibodi Nursing School (Reel 43, Frame 653)
    - Thailand - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/617.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 43, Frame 681)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/617.E
      - Thailand - Fellowships (Reel 43, Frame 723)
      - A-V (Reel 43, Frame 736)
    - Thailand - Social Sciences, 1970/617.S
      - University of Thammasat (Economics) (Reel 43, Frame 913)
  - Southeast Asia, 1970/625
    - L-S (Reel 44, Frame 1)
  - Holland, 1970/650
    - C-V (Reel 44, Frame 26)
  - Indonesia, 1970/652
    - A-U (Reel 44, Frame 144)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/652.E
      - Effendi, Surjatna (Reel 44, Frame 175)
  - Surinam (formerly Dutch Guiana), 1970/659
    - Central Laboratory (de Haas, R. A.) (Reel 44, Frame 177)
  - Europe, 1970/700
    - European North American Committee (Reel 44, Frame 180)
  - Ethiopia, 1970/701
    - A-H (Reel 44, Frame 217)
    - Ethiopia - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/701.E
      - Ethiopia (Reel 44, Frame 260)
      - Gebreab, Newaye (Reel 44, Frame 262)
  - Afghanistan, 1970/703
    - A-N (Reel 44, Frame 266)
  - Belgium, 1970/707
    - C-U (Reel 44, Frame 278)
  - Zaire, 1970/709
    - A-L (Reel 44, Frame 303)
    - Zaire - Medical Sciences, 1970/709.A
      - Lovanium University (Reel 44, Frame 375)
    - Zaire - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/709.E
      - N-R (Reel 44, Frame 381)
  - Bulgaria, 1970/711
    - Institute of Public Health (Reel 44, Frame 389)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1970/712
    - C-R (Reel 44, Frame 393)
  - Denmark, 1970/713
    - A-W (Reel 44, Frame 404)
  - Germany, 1970/717
    - A-W (Reel 44, Frame 465)
  - Tanzania, 1970/723
    - M-U (Reel 44, Frame 587)
    - Tanzania - Medical Sciences, 1970/723.A
      - University of Dar es Salaam (Medical School) (Reel 44, Frame 609)
    - Tanzania - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/723.E
      - K-W (Reel 44, Frame 616)
  - Zambia, 1970/724
    - University of Zambia (G-R) (Reel 44, Frame 635)
    - Zambia - Medical Sciences, 1970/724.A
      - University of Zambia (Medical School) (Reel 44, Frame 678)
  - Cameroon, 1970/735
    - Mafe, Mr. (Reel 44, Frame 682)
  - Greece, 1970/749
    - Thessalonica Agricultural and Industrial Institute (Reel 44, Frame 684)
  - Hungary, 1970/750
    - Hungary - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1970/750.D
      - Agriculture (Reel 44, Frame 694)
  - Italy, 1970/751
    - A-U (Reel 44, Frame 697)
  - Liberia, 1970/759
    - Cuttington College (Economics) (Reel 44, Frame 840)
  - Morocco, 1970/765
    - H-U (Reel 44, Frame 864)
    - Morocco - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/765.E
      - H-J (Reel 44, Frame 899)
  - Norway, 1970/767
    - B-U (Reel 44, Frame 913)
    - Norway - Social Sciences, 1970/767.S
      - University of Oslo (Economic Institute) (Reel 44, Frame 951)
  - Iran, 1970/771
    - F-U (Reel 44, Frame 953)
    - Iran - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/771.E
      - Khazra, Houshang (Reel 44, Frame 1022)
  - Portugal, 1970/773
    - E-N (Reel 44, Frame 1027)
  - Romania, 1970/783
    - Ilea, Viorel (Reel 44, Frame 1046)
  - USSR, 1970/785
    - Ositov, Gennadij (Reel 44, Frame 1052)
  - Finland, 1970/787
    - University (H-T) (Reel 44, Frame 1054)
  - Poland, 1970/789
    - L-U (Reel 44, Frame 1057)
  - Spain, 1970/795
    - B-U (Reel 44, Frame 1067)
  - Sweden, 1970/800
    - L-U (Reel 44, Frame 1086)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/800.E
      - Erjefalt, Lennart (Reel 44, Frame 1123)
  - Liechtenstein, 1970/802
    liechtenstein
    - Liechtenstein, Karolina (Reel 44, Frame 1131)
  - Switzerland, 1970/803
    - C-V (Reel 44, Frame 1137)
  - Turkey, 1970/805
    - H-Y (Reel 45, Frame 1)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Training Awards, 1970/805.E
      - Turkey - Fellowships (Reel 45, Frame 262)
      - A-Y (Reel 45, Frame 264)
  - United Arab Republic (Egypt), 1970/812
    - A-N (Reel 45, Frame 277)
  - Israel, 1970/825
    - B-T (Reel 45, Frame 287)
  - Lebanon, 1970/833
    - American University of Beirut (A-W) (Reel 45, Frame 368)
  - Members and Meetings, 1970/903
    - Bingham, Barry (Reel 45, Frame 385)
    - Bunche, Ralph J. (Reel 45, Frame 395)
    - Dickey, John S. (Reel 45, Frame 402)
    - Dillon, C. Douglas (Reel 45, Frame 405)
    - Franks of Headington, Oliver Shewell, Baron (Reel 45, Frame 407)
    - Houghton, Arthur A., Jr. (Reel 45, Frame 418)
    - Kerr, Clark (Reel 45, Frame 424)
    - Lleras Camargo, Alberto (Reel 45, Frame 430)
    - Moyers, Bill D. (Reel 45, Frame 433)
    - Notices (Reel 45, Frame 436)
    - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd (Reel 45, Frame 513)
    - Rockefeller, John D. 4th (Reel 45, Frame 524)
    - Roosa, Robert V. (Reel 45, Frame 530)
    - Seitz, Frederick (Reel 45, Frame 532)
    - Stanton, Frank (Reel 45, Frame 547)
    - Vance, Cyrus R. (Reel 45, Frame 550)
    - Watson, Thomas J., Jr. (Reel 45, Frame 554)
    - Wharton, Clifton R., Jr. (Reel 45, Frame 560)
    - Wood, W. Barry, Jr. (Reel 45, Frame 562)
    - Young, Whitney M., Jr. (Reel 45, Frame 565)